A Guide to the 8th Evacuation Hospital 1941-2011
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Lewis Kirkman ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 2.5 x 3.5 (Box-folder 11-029)
- Byrd Leavell ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.25 (Box-folder 11-030)
- Dish washing tent for patients' mess ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-031)
- Group photo of officers and nurses ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 4 x 5, 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-032)
  left to right: Kinkopf, McNeel, Winthrop, Drash, Beery, McKoan, McCone, Blackford, Holmboe, Suhling
- Byrd Leavell ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.75 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-033)
- Winter in Pietramala, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-034)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-58
- Staige Blackford, Byrd Leavell, John McNeel ND, PHOTOS 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-035)
- Lewis Kirkman ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.5 x 3.5 (Box-folder 11-036)
- Outside Ward 10 ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.5 x 3.5 (Box-folder 11-037)
  Lewis Kirkman in the center
- Francis Churchill, Herbert Martin, Leonard Dixon, Ruth Beery ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-038)
- Joseph Martin, unidentified man, Lewis Kirkman 1945 December 25, PHOTO 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-039)
- Joseph Martin, unidentified man, E. Cato Drash, unidentified man ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-040)
- wedding day ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-041)
  Ted Laird, unidentified woman, Staige Blackford, Frances Wells Broadfoot (bride), Fred Broadfoot (groom), Ted Marks (best man) in Florence, Italy
- John Garfield on left with unidentified men ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.75 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-042)
- Kitchen clean-up area 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-043)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-45-754
- Patients coming through the mess line 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-044)
- Ruth Eastman, Lelia Langhorn Cloyd ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-045)
- Left to right: Staige Blackford, Samuel Casscells, Ruth Beery, 2 unidentified men ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-046)
- Scrub room 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-047)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-590
- Instrument room where instruments were washed, sterilized and wrapped 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-048)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-594
- Wedding of Beatrice Ramsey and Jim Boston 1945 August 25, PHOTO 1-B&W 6.75 x 8.25 (Box-folder 11-049)
  Women L-R: Beery, Robinson, Matthews, bridal couple, Wiseman, Franklin, Brusati; Men L-R: unidentified man, Martin, unidentified man, Leavell, Marshall, Ted Laird
- John McKoan Pinning a medal on Prentice Kinser ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7.25 (Box-folder 11-050)
- Samuel Windham (?) and Kate Robinson in Caserta, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.5 x 6.5 (Box-folder 11-051)
- Elizabeth Harlin ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 5.25 (Box-folder 11-052)
- unidentified General and William Snavely ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-053)
- Eruption of Mount Vesuvius 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-054)
  photograph taken and donated by William Snavely
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-055)
- Chaplain James Fleming on right with two unidentified men ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-056)
- Frances Scott Carter (Red Cross) with Robert Mitchell to her right, others unidentified men ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3 x 4.75 (Box-folder 11-057)
- Kitchen cook stoves 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-058)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-551
- Chaplain Bill Laird giving chapel service for patients in Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-059)
- Jack Gordon and Joseph Hardigan in Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.75 (Box-folder 11-060)
- Jack Gordon and unidentified man in Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4. 75 (Box-folder 11-061)
- Tents after a storm ND, PHOTOS 8-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-062)
- Harold Rupe demonstrates new system for medicinal packing at 8th Evac 1944 March 7, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-063)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C/MM-5-44-100403
- People standing and clapping ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-064)
  Left to right: Kidd, unidentified woman, Dofflemeyer, unidentified woman, Huffman, unidentified man
- Nurses eating ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-065)
  Left to right: Hornbarger, Ramsey, Canniff
- Herbert Martin is commissioned by Kirkman, Ruth Beery in front of the nurses 1945 February, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-066)
- McKoan in center of group at party ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-067)
- Patients' mess tent 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-068)
- Patients in ward tent 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-069)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-5
- Group standing outside Ward #7 ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.5 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-070)
  Left to right: Corpsman, patient, patient, Wiseman, Blackford, Beery
- Angela Brusati ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-071)
- Martin facing photographer, Drash in center with back to photographer ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.5 x 5 (Box-folder 11-072)
- Hospital tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5.25 (Box-folder 11-073)
- Nurses and soldier on board ship returning to USA from Naples, Italy 1945 November, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-074)
  far left: Hornbarger, far right: Sandridge
- Cooks in the mess tent kitchen packing food 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-075)
- Kinkopf at Pietramala, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-076)
- Personnel surrounding man playing a violin ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-077)
  Smith, Linus Miller, Leavell, Northrup, Gilkerson, Beery, Boston (not 8th Evac), Tolliver(not 8th Evac), Dick Morris (?)
- Hornbarger, Beery, 3 unidentified people ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-078)
- Snow, tents, and ambulances in Pietramala, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-079)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-
- Gordon (?), Dempsey, and McNeel releasing pigeons ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-080)
- Group at party ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-081)
  Monin, Canniff, Laird, Wiseman, Ramsey, Weller, Blackford, Culbertson, Hrejsa, Miller identified as being in photo
- 8th Evac tents with hillside in background, near Florence, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-082)
- 8th Evac tents, aerial view ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4.25 x 6.5 (Box-folder 11-083)
- Stimson in pith helmet followed by Clark, Drash to right of Clark, Martin last on right in front 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.5 x 5 (Box-folder 11-084)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-45-739-3
- Hospital tents in Southern Italy, water in background ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7.5 (Box-folder 11-085)
- Drash and Kinkopf ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.75 x 4.5 (Box-folder 11-086)
- Snow and tents in Pietramala, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-087)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-586
- Moving day ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 6 (Box-folder 11-088)
  Kirkman (on right), Mapp to the left of Kirkman, packing boxes made by 8th Evac shop were also used as desks
- men in mess tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-089)
  3rd from left: Holmboe, 5th from left: Drash, others are unidentified
- Moving day ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-090)
  Tim Holt (?), Guerrant, Shearburn, Al Den (?), Holsinger, Eula Wright and Ted Laird in photo
- Nursing office, Beery on right ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-091)
- 8th Evac at Anzio, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-092)
- Joint used on corner of tables ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-093)
  designed by Randal Luscombe
- Ward tent with patients, one with Esquire magazine ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-094)
- Drash pinning Beery in front of nurses ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-095)
- Vivian Gillespie (left) and Kate Robinson relaxing in tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 11-096)
- Drash ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.5 x 5 (Box-folder 11-097)
- Operating tent-not in use ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-098)
- 8th Evac nurses presented to King George VI by Lt. Gen. Mark Clark at Cecina, Italy 1944, PHOTOS 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-099)
- Nurses and officers on ski holiday at Pietramala, Italy; left to right: Waddell, Bell, Huffman, Casscells, Franklin ND, PHOTOS 1-B&W 5 x 7, 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-100)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology photos
- Huffman pinning new bars on Snavely ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 11-101)
- Nurse Roadcap relaxing and reading Stars and Stripes in tent in Pietramala, Italy 1944 December, PHOTO B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-102)
- Officers relaxing at Fifth Army Rest Center, Rome, Snavely on left ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-103)
- Nurse Wiseman preparing to move, Carinola, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 11-104)
- Huffman and Cloyd outside tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.5 x 3.25 (Box-folder 11-105)
- Unidentified man and Roger Mapp standing outside officers' mess tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 12-001)
- Dignitaries in operating tent with patient, Kirkman in back to right, mostly hidden ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-002)
- Left to right: Kirkman, unidentified man, Drash, and unidentified man in pharmacy, medical supply tent ND, PHOTO B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-003)
- Anfa Hotel in Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-004)
- Tom Michie on left, 3 unidentified men ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-005)
- Left to right: unidentified man, Holmboe, Forrestal, Kirkman ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-006)
- Stimson and Drash coming out of tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-007)
- Left to right: Martin, unidentified man, Kirkman, and Holmboe with a medal ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-008)
- Left to right: Martin, Holmboe, Kirkman ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-009)
- Camels in Africa ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-010)
- Bikes in North Africa town ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-011)
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-012)
  Blackford, Wray, Michie, Laird, all facing camera
- African scene ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-013)
- Fortress in Africa ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-014)
- Group of men standing outside 1944, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-015)
  Colonel Bruce, Asst. Surgeon, 5th Army, 1 unidentified man, Forrestal, Kirkman, unidentified man, Drash in Cecina, Italy
- Far left: Clark, middle: Stimson in front of tents, 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-016)
- Secretary of the Navy Forrestal visits the 8th Evac., Cecina, Italy 1944 August, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-017)
  Left to right: McNeel, unidentified man, Forrestal, Drash; Armed Forces Institute of Pathology photo
- Stimson in pith helmet followed by Clark, Drash to right of Clark, Martin last on right in front 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-018)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-45-739-
- 8th Evac honorary plaque ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-019)
- Sandbags at entrance to 8th Evac hospital at Le Ferriere, Italy 1944 June, PHOTO B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-020)
- Part of a wedding party sitting in a jeep 1944 April 11, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-021)
  left to right: John McKoan, unidentified man, Angela Brusati (bridesmaid), Marie Galvin (first 8th Evac nurse to become a bride "in the field"); Armed Forces Institute of Pathology photo
- Secretary of War Stimson and Lt. Gen. Clark (in back seat of jeep) visit the 8th Evac, 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-022)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-45-739-4
- Soldiers inspecting captured German half-track, Grosetto, Italy 1944 June-July, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 and 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-023)
- Mark Clark (left) and Stimson (pith helmet) shown into operating tent by Drash, ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-024)
- Convoy of trucks carrying 8th Evac's equipment through Rome 1944 June 16, PHOTOS 1-B&W 5 x 7 and 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-025)
- Aerial view of set up at Carinola, Italy 1944, PHOTOS 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-026)
- Holmboe in center ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-027)
- Dead German soldier at Pietramala ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-028)
- McNeel, Stimson, unidentified man, Mark Clark ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-029)
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-030)
  left to right: Blackford, Wray, Michie, Laird
- Tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-031)
- Unidentified man, Marshall, Monin, unidentified man, Holsinger, and Bell visiting ruins ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-032)
- Water tower at 8th Evac ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-033)
- North Africa scene ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-034)
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-035)
  Blackford, Wray, Michie, Laird at table
- Officers' quarters in Jewish school in Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-036)
- McNeel, Weller, Forrestal, unidentified man;, McNeel and Forrestal looking at book ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-037)
- Four men outside tents (probably not 8th Evac) ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-038)
- Soldiers outside receiving tent (probably not 8th Evac) ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-039)
- Scene of destruction, burning ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 12-040)
- Scene of destruction ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-041)
- Moving day ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-042)
- Men standing, Michie second from left ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-043)
- Irving Berlin in center, Holmboe on right ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-044)
- Irving Berlin and Holmboe ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-045)
- Aerial view of hospital tents and surrounding area ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-046)
- Party outside ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-047)
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-048)
- Crotts second from left, relaxing ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-049)
- Groups outside with jeep and tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-050)
  : Bell, first man on left; Alice Huffman, facing camera to left of woman in white; Sherman, first on right in front group
- McNeel and Stimson with book ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-051)
- Two-star general in center, McNeel behind and to left of general ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-052)
- Snavely on right in Pietramala, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-053)
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-054)
  Blackford, Wray, Michie and Laird at table
- Scene of destruction ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-055)
- View of ships at sea ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-056)
- Personnel, including nurses, standing at attention and some saluting ND, PHOTOS 3-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-057)
- Tents and water tank ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-058)
- Awarding the first Purple Heart ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-059)
  McKoan, Kinkopf, Blackford, McNeel, Gillespie (?), Suhling present but not specifically identified in photo
- General Allen and General Martin, McKoan hidden ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-061)
- Two unidentified men in town ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-062)
- Four nurses in front of tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-063)
  left to right: unidentified woman, Hornbarger, unidentified woman, Wiseman in front of tent at Anfa Hill near Casablanca
- Group of military personnel sitting outside as an audience ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-064)
  Northrup on far left, Jane Anderson second from left, Holsinger on right with pipe
- Tents at Cap Matifou, Algiers ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 6.5 (Box-folder 12-065)
- McKoan, General Allen, General Martin, Colonel H. John (?), Kinkopf at inspection ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-066)
- Mess facilities at Capua, Italy 1943, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-067)
- 8th Evac tents with hillside in background, near Florence, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-068)
- Rear view of supply tent; water for scrubbing ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-069)
- Allied destruction in Naples, Italy harbor ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-070)
- Tents at Teano, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-071)
- Tents at Anfa Hill near Casablanca 1943, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-072)
- John McNeel ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-073)
- Jenkins, Drash, Martin, Martin gets promotion ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-074)
- Hubert Holsinger ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5.5 and 1-B&W 5 x 6.5 (Box-folder 12-075)
- Patients and beds in ward at Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-076)
- Hospital tents near Florence, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-077)
- Outdoor scene, North Africa (?) ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-078)
- Tents, maybe near Florence ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-079)
- Unidentified men and women at tables ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4.75 x 6.5 (Box-folder 12-080)
- Tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-081)
- Drash reading citation for Sgt. Martin ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-082)
- Outdoor scene with unidentified people ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-083)
- Headquarters at Teano, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-084)
- Trucks arriving at Anzio, Italy 1944 June, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-085)
- Volleyball game at living quarters at Jewish school, Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-086)
- Nurses at attention ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-087)
- Three unidentified men ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-088)
- McKoan and two unidentified women ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-089)
- Probably x-ray section ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-090)
  Harry Dumbleton second from right in back row, John Mapp bottom row in middle
- Dental clinic in the Italian Consulate ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-091)
  left to right: patient, George Northrup, Frederick Neumeister
- Group photo, unidentified ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-092)
- Officers mess (not 8th Evac) ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5.5 x 8.5 (Box-folder 12-093)
- Palm tress (North Africa?) ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-094)
- Vehicles and tent 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-095)
- Italian Consulate building in Casablanca 1942, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 1-B&W 5 x 6.5 (Box-folder 12-096)
- Monin, Driscoll, Miller, Smith, and Bell at Caserta, Italy 1943, PHOTO 1-B&W 4.75 x 6.5 (Box-folder 12-097)
- Move from Italian Consulate in Casablanca to Anfa Hill 1943, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-098)
- Patients in courtyard in Casablanca ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-099)
- Bathing party at Anzio, Italy 1944 June, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-100)
  "Les Poseurs" The Posers
- Hairfield and Thornton ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 12-101)
- Unidentified woman in supply tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-001)
  shows ward boxes designed and organized by the 8th Evac; Armed Forces Institute of Pathology photo
- Tents at Capua, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-002)
- Operating tent prior to modification ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-003)
- Colonel Bruce, Asst. Surgeon, 5th Army, Forrestal, Kirkman, unidentified man, Drash 1944 August, PHOTOS 3-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-004)
- Enlisted men at work in the 8th Evac utilities tent 1945 January 13, PHOTOS 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-005)
- Ambulances waiting to load patients for evacuation to base hospitals, Le Ferriere, Italy 1944 June, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-006)
- Linus Miller on moving day at Cellole, Italy 1944 may, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-007)
- Pitching a tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-008)
- Staige Blackford ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-0-9)
- Party for departing commanding officer at Carinola, Italy 1944 April, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-010)
- Laboratory of the 8th Evac, Italy 1945 January 13, PHOTO B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-011)
  Fletcher Spann and John Dawson at work (unclear which man is which)
- Group picture of 8th Evac officers and nurses, tents in background, Italy 1944 Summer, PHOTOS 3-B&W 8 x 10, 1-B&W 7.5 x 9.5 (Box-folder 13-012)
- Group picture of servicemen being entertained by a "G.I." show in Carinola, Italy 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-013)
- Two unidentified men in front of the 8th Evac Hospital sign, Lake Garda, Italy 1945, PHOTOS 1-B&W 2.5 x 3.5 and 1-B&W 2.25. x 3.5 (Box-folder 13-014)
- Two unidentified men in front of tents 1945, PHOTO 1-B&W 3 x 3.75 (Box-folder 13-015)
- Inside dishwashing ten for patients' mess ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-016)
- Unidentified men outside tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 6 (Box-folder 13-017)
- Unidentified man at food table ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.5 x 3.25 (Box-folder 13-018)
- Wounded patient in operating tent 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-019)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-558
- 8th Evac landing in Italy near Paestum and Salerno 1943 September 21, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-020)
- Moving day ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 13-021)
  left to right: Hilda Franklin, unidentified woman, and F. Jean Williams
- Ruins of a building ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.25 x 3 (Box-folder 13-022)
- Bird on path between tents ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.5 x 3 (Box-folder 13-023)
- Scrambling for firewood before rationing and distribution, Tav Toricello ND, PHOTOS 2-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-024)
- Inside the X-ray tent ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-025)
- Inside the 8th Evac X-ray room 1945 January 13, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-026)
  J. L. Knight, an X-ray technician, gives a chest X-ray; Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. 5/MM-45-767
- Beach south of Casablanca 1943 Spring, PHOTO 1-B&W 7 x 9.5 (Box-folder 13-027)
- 8th Evac reunion ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 8 x 10 (Box-folder 13-028)
  left to right: Kate Robinson, Byrd Leavell, Betty Johnson, John Guerrant, Bea Ramsey
- 8th Evac reunion photo of men around table 1960, PHOTOS 1-B&W 8 x 10, 1-B&W 7.5 x 9.5, mounted (Box-folder 13-029)
  seated left to right: Pat Driscoll, Cato Drash, Norman Thornton, John Guerrant; standing: Maury LeBauer, Hubert Holsinger, James Culberton, John Morris, Al Gillespie, Rich Low. Photographed by Ralph Thompson
- Applying a cast to an orthopedic patient 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-030)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. MM-5-44-2179
- Tents and personnel ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.75 x 4.75 (Box-folder 13-031)
- Boat sunk in Naple's harbor 1943, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-032)
- Jefferson Day celebration ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-033)
  left to right: Wray, Blackford, Michie, William Laird
- Representative Clare booth Luce at 8th Evac 1945 March 21, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-034)
  Luce visits patient Julius Hartfell during her tour of the Fifth Army Front; Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. 5/MM-45-4984
- 8th Evac nurses at attention ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-035)
- Wedding day 1944 April 11, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-036)
  Left to right: Angela Brusati (bridesmaid), John McKoan, Marie Galvin, the first 8th Evac nurse to become a bride "in the field"
- Tents and the Hippodrome for movies ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-037)
- Lake Garda, Italy ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 3.25 x 4.5 (Box-folder 13-038)
- Ambulance ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.25 x 3.25 (Box-folder 13-039)
- Inside of officers' mess tent 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-040)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology C-44-552
- Small utility table at 8th Evac, Teano area, Italy 1944 March 9, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-041)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. MM-5-44-2178
- Ruins ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-042)
- Ruins ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-043)
- Winterized operating room in use 1944, PHOTO 1-B&W 4 x 5 (Box-folder 13-044)
  Armed Forces Institute of Pathology Neg. No. C-44-555
- Operating room ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 5 x 7 (Box-folder 13-045)
- Stimson in pith helmet ND, PHOTO 1-B&W 2.75 x 4.5 (Box-folder 13-046)